I stored this page element inside of the "card" variable.
لقد خزّنت عنصر الصفحة داخل متغير "البطاقة".
Now let's compare the card's text content property with its innerText property.
لنقارن الآن خاصية المحتوى النصي للبطاقة بخاصية innerText له.
But before we do that,
لكن قبل أن نفعل ذلك،
let's actually hide some of the text with CSS.
دعونا نخفي بعضًا من النص باستخدام CSS.
Here we can see the "New!",
يمكننا أن نرى "جديد!" هنا،
the "Data Foundation's Nanodegree" and the "Enroll Now" text,
و"برنامج Nanodegree لتعلم أساسيات البيانات"، ونص "تسجيل الآن"،
but over here on the element itself we only see
هنا فوق العنصر نفسه، لن نتمكن سوى من رؤية
"New" and then "Data Foundations Nanodegree".
"جديد" و"برنامج Nanodegree لتعلم أساسيات البيانات".
We don't actually see the words "Enroll Now" which were down
لن نرى الكلمات "تسجيل الآن" التي كانت توجد بالأسفل
here because I hid them with CSS, display none.
لأنني أخفيتها باستخدام CSS، عدم عرض أي شيء.
So, let's check out the card's text content property.
حسنًا، لنتحقق من خاصية المحتوى النصي للبطاقة.
And this shows us all of the text of the element.
يوضح لنا ذلك النص الكامل الموجود في العنصر.
Now let's compare that with innerText.
لنقارن الآن ذلك بخاصية innerText.
We can see that the innerText property does not have the text "Enroll Now".
يمكننا أن نرى أن خاصية innerText لا تحتوي على النص "تسجيل الآن".
It's missing from down here,
إنها لا توجد بالأسفل هنا،
but there's also new is all in caps up here,
لكن يوجد أيضًا كلما جديد "new" مكتوبة بأحرف كبيرة بالكاملة،
while new actually is only capital N as you can see up here.
في حين أن كلمة جديد "new" لم تُكتب سوى بحرف كبير واحد فقط وهو N كما رأينا هنا.
The text content property returns all of the text regardless if CSS.
تعمل خاصية المحتوى النصي بإرجاع النص بالكامل بغض النظر عن CSS.
The innerText property returns the text as it would be seen visually.
أما خاصية innerText، إنها ترجع النص كما رأيناه في السابق.